Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Programs, Posters and other Printed Materials
    - Regular and Summer Season Programs
      - 1951-1952 Season
        - The Rope; The Tenor, October 24, 1951; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - The Vegetable, November 1-4, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Wurzel-Flummery, November 7, 1951; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Cornell One-Act Plays (The Late Adam Fry; The Big Cheese; The Fishbowl), November 17, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Riders to the Sea, November 20, 1951; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Two One-Act Plays (Wurzel Flummery; The Fishbowl), November 27, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Fumed Oak; Troilus and Cressida, December 5, 1951; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - The Madwoman of Chaillot, December 13-16, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - On the High Road, December 18, 1951; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Where the Cross Is Made, January 15, 1952; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Romeo and Juliet, February 1-2, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Desire Under the Elms, February 21-24, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - The Pirates of Penzance, March 5-9, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Dirt Below Stairs; The Clod; The Ring of General Macias, March 20, 1952; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - The Family Reunion, April 17-20, 1952; Laboratory Players (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Awake and Sing!, May 8-11, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - Deirdre, May 14, 1952; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - The School for Wives, June 6-8, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
      - Summer 1952
        - Tambou, July 10-12, 1952; Ithaca Community Players (Box 43A, Folder 71)
        - The Family Reunion, July 18-19, 1952; Laboratory Players (Box 43A, Folder 71)
        - Yes M'Lord, July 25-26, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 71)
        - Village Wooing; Hello Out There, August 1-2, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 71)
        - Is Life Worth Living, August 8-9, 1952 (Box 43A, Folder 71)
      - 1952-1953 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 20, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - You Never Can Tell, October 23-26, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Twelve Pound Look, October 30, 1952; Actors' Lab Series (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Ten Nights in a Bar-Room, November 13-16, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Long Christmas Dinner, December 13, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Valiant; The Little Stone House, December 17, 1952; Actors' Lab Series (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Hay Fever, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 1)
          Includes January 16-17 and February 6-7
        - Juno and the Paycock, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Informer; Waiting for Lefty, March 5, 1953; Actors' Lab Series (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Patience, March 11-15, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Bar-Room Incident; No Other Way, March 26, 1953; Actors' Lab Series (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Autumn Garden, April 16-18, 1953; Laboratory Players (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Trojan Horse, April 25, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - "Homecoming," Act 1 from Mourning Becomes Electra; Hope Is The Thing With Feathers, April 30, 1953; Actors' Lab Series (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - The Tempest, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Summer 1953 (30th)
        - The Autumn Garden, July 17-18, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Overruled; Master Pierre Patelin, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - The Circle, August 7-8, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Some Final Innocence, August 10, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - 1953-1954 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 19, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - The Country Wife, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 3)
          Includes October 29-31 and November 1
        - The Glass Menagerie, November 19-22, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - The Christmas Invasion ("A Good Old-Fashioned Christmas"; "Christmas Eve"; "The Line"; The Christmas Story according to St. Luke), December 11, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Wurzel-Flummery; In the Shadow of the Glen, December 16, 1953; Studio '54 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - The Lady's Not for Burning, January 14-17, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Hedda Gabler, February 25-28, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Three One-Act Plays (Paradiso! Paradiso!; Two Worlds to Conquer; The Long Voyage Home), March 19, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - The Inspector-General, April 23-25, 1954; Laboratory Players (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - This Music Crept By Me Upon the Waters, April 27, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Iolanthe, May 12-16, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Quare Medicine; Second Degree, May 20, 1954; Studio '54 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - The Male Animal, June 11-13, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Summer 1954
        - So Long, July 23-24, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - The Old Ladies, August 6-7, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - 1954-1955 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 18, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Charley's Aunt, October 21-24, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Thor, With Angels, December 11-12, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Ties That Bind (Among Friends, Moony's Kid Don't Cry, The Ping-Pong Players), January 15, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Twelfth Night, February 17-20, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Street Scene, March 17-20, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Blood Wedding, April 22-24, 1955; Laboratory Players (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Twelfth Night, June 10-12, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Summer 1955
        - Candida, July 20, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - 1955-1956 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 17, 22, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - The Skin of Our Teeth, October 27-30, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - The Stallion, November 10, 1955; Studio '56 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Right You Are, November 17-20, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Amahl and the Night Visitors (preceded by The Gift of the Magi), December 15-17, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Electra, March 8-11, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - The Flowering Peach, April 12-15, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - The Would-Be Invalid (Le Malade Imaginaire), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 7)
          Includes May 10-13 and June 8-10
      - Summer 1956
        - Arms and the Man, July 18, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - 1956-1957 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 15, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Misalliance, October 25-28, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Kagekiyo, November 1, 1956; Studio '57 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - All Summer Long, November 15-18, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Bernardine, December 13-16, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Once Upon a Hill, January 11, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Miss Julia; Mr. Sleeman Is Coming, January 17, 1957; Studio '57 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - The Good Woman of Setzuan, 1957; Laboratory Players (Box 44, Folder 9)
          Includes February 28 and March 1-3
        - Box and Cox; The Romancers, March 14, 1957; Studio '57 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - The Witchfinders, April 11-14, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Favor Island, April 25, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Papa is All, May 9-12, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Roommate; Gomennasai, May 16, 1957; Studio '57 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Summer 1957
        - Major Barbara, July 17, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - 1957-1958 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 21, 26, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - This Property Is Condemned; A Sunny Morning, October 24, 1957; Studio '58 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - The Tavern, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 11)
          Includes October 31 and November 1-3
        - Amahl and the Night Visitors (preceded by The Fountain of Youth), December 12-15, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Othello, January 16-19, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - How He Lied to Her Husband; Hello Out There, February 27, 1958; Studio '58 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Shadow and Substance, March 6-9, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Everyman, March 20, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - A Different Drummer, April 17-20, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Give to Me a Golden Star; Moon Hound, May 1, 1958; Studio '58 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - The Haunted House, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 11)
          Includes May 15-18 and June 13-15
      - 1958-1959 Season (50th)
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 22, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Bell, Book and Candle, October 23-26, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - The Rivals, December 11-14, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Antigone, January 15-18, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Ghosts, March 5-8, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - The Taming of the Shrew, May 14-17, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - 1959-1960 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 21, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Time of Harvest; The Game of Chess, October 15, 1959; Studio '60 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - My Three Angels, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - The Boy Friend, December 10-13, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Death of a Salesman, January 14-17, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Dr. Faustus, March 3-6, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Saint Joan, scene IV; The Death of Odysseus, March 10, 1960; Studio '60 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Twilight Bar, April 21-24, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - The School for Husbands, May 12-15, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - 1960-1961 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 20, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Private Lives, November 10-13, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Thieves' Carnival, December 8-11, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Pictures in the Hallway, January 12-14, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Three Russian Comedies (Gamblers; A Marriage Proposal; Squaring the Circle), March 2, 9-12, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Medea, April 13-16, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Volpone, May 11-14, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - 1961-1962 Season
        - The Time of Your Life, November 9-12, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - The Great God Brown, December 14-17, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - John Brown's Body, February 15-18, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - The Gondoliers, March 7-11, 1962; Produced with the Savoyards (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - Three Way Split (The Sandbox; The Room; The Future is in Eggs), April 12-15, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - How to Grow a Musical, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
          Includes May 10-13 and June 9-10, 16-18
      - 1962-1963 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 18, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - A Taste of Honey, October 24-28, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - Man and Superman, November 15-18, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - Rashomon, December 13-16, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - Oedipus the King, January 10-13, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - The Women at the Tomb, February 24, 1963; Dept. of Speech and Drama - Drummond Studio (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - As You Like It, March 7-10, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - J.B., April 11-14, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - The Chairs; Krapp's Last Tape, April 24-28, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - The Fantasticks, May 9-12, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Summer 1963
        - U.S.A., July 9, 11, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - 1963-1964 Season
        - Lysistrata, November 7-10, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - Rosmersholm, January 16-19, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - Romeo and Juliet, March 12-15, 20-22, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - Look Back in Anger, April 16-19, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - The Mistress of the Inn, May 14-17, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Summer 1964
        - Finnegans Wake, July 8-12, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - Endgame, July 14-15, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - The Well of the Saints, July 22-26, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - The Apple Cart (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - The Willow Copse, August 5-9, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - 1964-1965 Season
        - Finnegans Wake, October 16-17, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 20)
        - The Jew of Malta, November 12-15, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 20)
        - The Happy Haven, December 3-6, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 20)
        - Tartuffe, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 20)
          Includes February 25-28 and March 5-7
        - The Great Magician, April 15-18, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 20)
        - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, May 13-16, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Summer 1965
        - The Philadelphia Story, July 7-11, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 21)
        - Telemachus Clay, July 16-17, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 21)
        - All the King's Men, July 21-25, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 21)
        - The Devil in America, July 30-31, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - 1965-1966 Season
        - The Man of Mode, November 4-7, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 22)
        - The Physicists, December 9-12, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 22)
        - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, March 3-6, 11-12, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 22)
        - Medusa, April 14-17, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 22)
        - Uncle Vanya, May 12-15, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Summer 1966
        - Three Modern Plays (Act Without Words I; The Difficult Hour III; The Bald Soprano), July 7-9, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 23)
        - Saint Joan of the Stockyards, July 15-17, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 23)
        - The Knack, July 21-23, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 23)
        - The Hostage, August 4-6, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 23)
        - The Gambler, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - 1966-1967 Season
        - The Knack, November 10-13, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 24)
        - King Richard III, December 15-18, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 24)
        - Dracula, February 16-19, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 24)
        - Andorra, March 16-19, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 24)
        - The Threepenny Opera, May 4-7, 11-14, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Summer 1967
        - The Deadly Game, July 6-8, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 25)
        - A Taste of Honey, July 13-15, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 25)
        - The Cave Dwellers, July 20-22, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 25)
        - The Blood Knot, July 27-29, 196(7?) (Box 44, Folder 25)
        - The Egg, August 3-5, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - 1967-1968 Season
        - Barthol'mew Fair, November 2-5, 10-11, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 26)
        - Getting Married, December 7-10, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 26)
        - Mary Stuart, February 15-18, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 26)
        - Zoo, March 14-17, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 26)
        - Orontea, May 9-11, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Summer 1968
        - Spoon River Anthology, July 5-6, 10-13, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 27)
        - John Brown's Body, July 18-20, 24-27, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - 1968-1969 Season (60th)
        - The Acharnians, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 28)
          Includes October 24-26, 31 and November 1-3
        - The School for Wives, December 12-15, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 28)
        - The Rules of the Game, March 5-9, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - 1969-1970 Season
        - Tango, March 12-15, 18-21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 29)
        - Lock Up Your Daughters, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 29)
          Includes April 30 and May 3, 6-9
      - 1971-1972 Season
        - The Rehearsal, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          Includes June 24-27; July 3, 8, 16, 25; August 3, 11
        - Juno and the Paycock, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          Includes July 1-2, 4, 9-11, 17, 31; August 2, 10
        - School for Scandal, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          Includes July 22-24, 29-30; August 1, 7, 12-13, 15
        - The Fantasticks, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          Includes July 1-2, 4, 9-11; August 4, 10
        - The Glass Menagerie, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          Includes June 24-27; July 3, 8, 16, 25; August 3, 5
        - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          Includes April 30 and May 6-7
        - The Ghost Sonata, March 2-5, 9-11, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 30)
        - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well And Living in Paris, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
          Includes June 22-25; July 1, 7, 12, 23; August 1, 9
        - Home, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
        - Happy Birthday, Wanda June, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
          Includes June 29-30; July 2, 8, 25, 29; August 2, 11
        - The Taming of the Shrew, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
          Includes July 5-6, 9, 14-15, 21, 26; August 3, 6, 12
        - What the Butler Saw, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
          Includes July 19-20, 22, 27-28, 30; August 4-5, 8, 10
        - Lady Windemere's Fan, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
        - Sunday Circus, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 31)
          Includes July 2, 9, 16, 23, 30; August 6
      - 1972-1973 Season
        - Storm Weather; The Boor, February 15-18, 1973; Studio Series (Box 44, Folder 31)
        - When We Dead Awaken, 1973; Studio Series (Box 44, Folder 31)
          Includes March 29 and April 1, 5-7
      - 1973-1974 Season
        - The Apple Tree, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 32)
          Includes July 27, 29; August 2, 4, 7, 10, 12, 16, 23, 30; September 6
        - The Country Wife, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 32)
          Includes August 17-18, 21-22, 25-26, 29; September 2, 8
        - Old Times, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 32)
          Includes October 25-28 and November 1-3
        - The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolda, November 8-11, 15-17, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 32)
        - Mary Stuart, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 32)
          Includes November 30 and December 2, 6-9
        - A Doll's House, March 7-10, 14-16, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - 1974-1975 Season
        - No Place to Be Somebody, October 17-20, 24-26, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 33)
        - A Streetcar Named Desire, March 6-9, 13-15, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - 1975-1976 Season
        - The Theatre Series, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 33a)
      - 1976-1977 Season
        - The Theatre Series, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 33b)
        - Ithaca Repertory Theatre Programs, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 88)
      - 1977-1978 Season
        - The Theatre Series, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 33c)
      - 1979-1982 Season
        - Other programs, 1979-1982 (Box 44, Folder 89)
      - 1990-1991 Season
        - Other programs, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 90)
      - 2007-2008 Season
        - The Bourgeois Gentleman, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 33d)
          Includes November 15-17, 29-30 and December 1
        - Love's Labour's Lost, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 33d)
          Includes November 20-22, and December 4-6
      - Undated
        - Great Variety Bill, undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - Grand Pill!; Hot Air!; 6 Plays in Search of a Rehearsal!, undated; Kernel Ham Actors-Izissa Theayter (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - A Kulinary Koncert, undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - The Hostage, undated; Cornell Summer Repertory Theatre (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - Two French Farces (Leonie is Early; Look, Don't Walk Around Naked), undated; Cornell Summer Repertory Theatre (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - The Martial Arts of Kubuki, undated; National Theater Institute of Japan (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - Filumena, undated; Cornell Summer Repertory Theatre (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - Charity Vaudeville, November 2-3, 1921 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Sponsored Performances
      - Tony Sarg's Marionettes
        - Rip Van Winkle, December 12, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - Sinbad the Sailor, November 17, 1932 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court, November 19, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - Faust, the Wicked Magician, November 19, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - Robinson Crusoe; The Mikado, December 4, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - Treasure Island, December 10, (no year) (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - The Tatterman Marionettes
        - The Glowing Bird; Stringing Broadway, July 15, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 36)
        - Legend of the Lightning; Stringing Broadway, circa 1932 (Box 44, Folder 36)
        - Peer Gynt, March 6, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 36)
        - The Glowing Bird, November 1, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - Four Irish Plays, January 20, 1921; The Shakespeare Playhouse (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Stuart Walker presents the Book of Job, November 23, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Adolph Bolm Dance Recital, March 20, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - The Rivals, May 4-5, 1926; Cornell University Women's Glee Club (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Thomas Wilfred in a Clavilux Recital, November 6, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - The Blue Bird; The Adventures of Huck Finn and Tom Sawyer, November 17, 1927; Jean Gros French Marionettes (Box 44, Folder 42)
      - Adolph Bolm Dance Recital, December 10, 1927 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - Ruth St. Denis, Ted Shawn and the Denishawn Dancers, November 24, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 44)
      - The Noyes School of Rhythm, October 18, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 45)
      - Thalia Zanou and Asya Kaz, Spanish dancers, December 11, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - Dance Recital - Harald Kreutzberg and his Group, April 23, 1932 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Tamiris, May 27, 1933 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Ted Shawn and his Ensemble of Men Dancers, 1933, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 48)
        Includes November 14, 1933; October 17, 1936
      - Miriam Winslow and her Dancers, October 19, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 49)
      - The Whiteheaded Boy, November 6, 1937; Hobart Little Theatre of Hobart and William Smith Colleges (Box 44, Folder 50)
      - Thomas Wilfred at the Clavilux, November 22, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 51)
      - Lady Precious Stream, March 12, 1938; Omnibus of Skidmore College (Box 44, Folder 52)
      - Arabian Nights: Aladdin and his Wonderful Lamp; Marco Millions, November 18, 1939; Jero Magon's Marionettes (Box 44, Folder 53)
      - Twelfth Night, November 16, 1940; The Chekhov Theatre Players (Box 44, Folder 54)
      - The Theatre of Angna Enters, February 22, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 55)
      - Alan Lomax and Leadbelly, March 21, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 56)
      - The Red Gate Players and their Chinese Shadow Plays, March 20, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 56)
      - The Glass Menagerie, 1949; Civic Theatre of Binghamton, Inc. (Box 44, Folder 57)
        Includes September 29-30 and October 1, 6-8
      - The Theatre of Angna Enters, February 11, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 58)
      - The Male Animal, October 14, 1950; Batavia Players (New York State Community Theatre Conference) (Box 44, Folder 59)
      - See How They Run, October 20, 1951; Cortland Community Players (Box 44, Folder 60)
      - Pygmalion, October 18, 1952; Newburgh Civic Theatre (Box 44, Folder 61)
      - Le Misanthrope, December 5-7, 1958; The Museum Theater Group (Box 44, Folder 62)
      - Endgame, March 20-22, 1959; The Museum Theater Group (Box 44, Folder 62)
      - The Matchmaker, October 29, 1962; Phoenix Theatre (Box 44, Folder 63)
      - Indonesian Dance, March 20, 1963; Hazel Chung (Box 44, Folder 64)
      - Six Characters in Search Of An Author, October 21, 1963; Circle in the Square Theatre (Box 44, Folder 65)
      - Brecht on Brecht, November 29-30, 1963; Lotte Lenya (Box 44, Folder 66)
      - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, October 22-24, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 67)
      - In White America, October 12-13, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 68)
      - The Royal Hunt of the Sun, October 15, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 69)
      - The Lion in Winter, February 10, 1968; Walter Slezak (Box 44, Folder 70)
      - Pictures in the Hallway, April 6, 1968; Paul Shyre (Box 44, Folder 71)
      - Les Danseurs Africains, September 27-28, 1968; L'ensemble National du Mali (Box 44, Folder 72)
      - America Hurrah, October 27, 1968; Stephanie Sills Productions, Inc. (Box 44, Folder 73)
      - By George, November 9, 1968; Max Adrian (Box 44, Folder 74)